Guide to the D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles archives, 1929-1995 and undated RL.00314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Benton & Bowles, 1929-1986 and undated, 26 boxes
  - Corporate Publications, 1938-1985 bulk 1940s-1985
    Includes primarily printed materials, as well as photographs and negatives, manuscript drafts of publications, and memoranda. The publications chronicle company history from 1947 to the 1980sMost of the runs for each publication are complete and they form the bulk of the section. Many of the stories about advertising campaigns center on human interest factors, such as the role of an actor in a commercial or a company event that launched the campaign. Organized into three sections: House Organs, Credentials, and Press Releases. The Credentials were created by Benton & Bowles to give prospective clients a general overview of the company and its services. House Organs focus primarily on news about the company, but also include a considerable amount of information about clients and advertising campaigns, management, domestic and international offices of Benton & Bowles subsidiary companies, corporate research, other advertising agencies, and various business, social, and personal activities of Benton & Bowles employees. The Press Releases include news about management changes, research reports, and clients. Credentials are arranged chronologically; House Organs, in alphabetical order by title, then chronologically; and Press Releases are in chronological order. See also oversize materials.
    - Credentials (Box B&B 8)
      - 1938, A History of Benton & Bowles...Nine Years Old This Summer (Box B&B 8)
      - 1939[?], Research Organization form letter (Box B&B 8)
      - 1943, A Presentation of the Services of Benton & Bowles (Box B&B 8)
      - 1955-1956, Questions and Answers About Benton & Bowles (Box B&B 8)
    - Credentials (Box B&B 9)
      - 1957, Dec., Hey! Where's Everybody (Relocation from Madison Ave. to Fifty Ave., N.Y.) (Box B&B 9)
      - 1958, Jan. 21, Buick: Benton & Bowles Is Right for Buick (an original notebook prepared for a day long meeting) (Box B&B 9)
      - 1958, Major U.S. Advertisers in Terms of Benton & Bowles' New Business Interest (Box B&B 9)
      - 1959, Facts About Benton & Bowles (Box B&B 9)
      - 1961, Credentials book (Box B&B 9)
      - 1962, Credentials book (Box B&B 9)
      - 1963, Business Development Program (Box B&B 9)
      - 1963, Some Notes from an Autobiography... Benton & Bowles, Inc. for Beech-Nut Life Savers, Inc. (Box B&B 9)
      - 1969-1972[?], This is Benton & Bowles, (B&B News Releases) (Box B&B 9)
      - 1960s[?], One Simple Selling Idea, Dramatically Presented (Box B&B 9)
      - 1970[?], This is Benton & Bowles (Box B&B 9)
      - 1971[?], Some Thoughts About Benton & Bowles (Box B&B 9)
      - 1974, It's Not Creative Unless It Sells (Box B&B 9)
    - Credentials (Box B&B 10)
      - 1977-1978, Profile of an International Advertising Agency (Box B&B 10)
      - 1978, Twenty Questions To Ask Before You Launch A New Product (Box B&B 10)
      - 1980, Introduction to Benton & Bowles (Box B&B 10)
    - Credentials
      - 1981-1982, B&B - Profile of an Advertising Agency (Box B&B 10)
      - 1982, Profile of an Advertising Agency, booklet update (Box B&B 10)
      - 1985, The Bright Stuff (Box B&B 10)
      - 1985, Quick Facts about B&B (Box B&B 10)
      - 1985[?], Sales (Box B&B 10)
    - House Organs
      - B&B Bulletin, 1947, Feb.-1948, Apr, 4 folders (Box B&B 10)
      - B&B Bulletin, (continued) 1948, May-1950, 8 folders (Box B&B 11)
      - B&B Bulletin, (continued) 1951-1958, 10 folders (Box B&B 12)
      - B&B Bulletin, (continued) 1959-1961, 5 folders (Box B&B 13)
      - B&B Bulletin, London Edition, 1962 (Box B&B 13)
      - B&B Europe Newsletter, 1979 (Box B&B 13)
      - B&B Impressions, 1968-1972 (Box B&B 13)
      - B&B Ink, Illustrations, 1982, Jan.-Feb(2 folders) (for copies of publication, see Oversize) (Box B&B 13)
      - B&B Ink, Illustrations (continued), 1982, Apr.-Oct, 9 folders (Box B&B 14)
      - B&B News, 1968, Apr.-1970, Feb, 2 folders (Box B&B 14)
      - B&B News, (continued) 1971-1981, 9 folders (Box B&B 15)
      - B&B Production News, 1968-1971 (Box B&B 15)
    - Press Releases, B&B News
      - 1941-1952, 1979-1985 (Box B&B 15)
      - 1980-1985 (Box B&B 15)
        [Clients: AMF; Apollo; J. Aron & Co.; Blistex; Corning Glass Works; Ericsson; Everstyl; Folio Society; Marine Midland Bank; Jeffrey Martin; Milliken & Co.; Brown Forman Distillers; Pinkerton Tobacco Co.; Prestel International; Quincy's Family Steakhouse; RCA Showtime; Refining; Texas Commerce Bankshares; UNICEF; Coalition for Literacy]
  - Subsidiary Companies, 1979-1980s
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, press releases, client lists, clippings, and printed material. Primarily documents Manning, Selvage and Lee, a public relations firm. There is information about its mission and the purchase of the firm by Benton & Bowles. There is little information about Medicus Communications or Riverview Productions. Arranged by subsidiary company name, and then chronologically with pictures at the end.
    - Manning, Slevage and Lee (Box B&B 15)
      - 1979, Nov. 21-1981, Sept. 24, undated (Box B&B 15)
      - Pictures, 1979-1980s, 2 folders (Box B&B 15)
    - Manning, Selvage and Lee, Pictures, 1979-1980s, 4 folders (Box B&B 16)
    - Medicus Communications, 1981, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Riverview Productions, Inc., 1985 (Box B&B 16)
  - Clients, 1931-1985, undated (bulk 1970-1980s, undated)
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, collateral literature (leaflets, brochures), press releases, notes, clippings, research records, printed material, photographs, and storyboards. Documents several aspects of advertising, including agreements for new advertising campaigns between Benton & Bowles and its clients; marketing strategies, including the early use of coupons; the adapting of advertising copy for use in local settings; the effectiveness of radio and television commercials; and the employment of celebrities in advertising campaigns. Clients most heavily represented include: Procter & Gamble Co.; General Foods; and Standard Brands. Additionally, there are research notes on consumer recall testing of television commercials for the Florida Citrus Commission, General Petroleum Company of Calif. (Mobil Oil), H.C. Moores Co. (Pream Instant Coffee Cream), and Texaco. Press releases about clients may be found in Corporate Publications. Arranged with a 1982 list of clients at the beginning of the series, then alphabetically by clients' names. Where the materials are further subdivided, they are arranged alphabetically by names of products; followed by correspondence, memoranda, and reports that are not product-specific.
    - Client list for B&B International, 1982 (Box B&B 16)
    - Avanti: Media Plan for 1983, 1982 (Box B&B 16)
    - AVCO Manufacturing Corp., Crosley Division, 1950s (Box B&B 16)
    - Bituminous Coal Institute, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Bolla Wines (see Jos. Garneau Co.) (Box B&B 16)
    - Can Manufacturers Institute, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Crosley (see AVCO) (Box B&B 16)
    - Eckrich (see Peter Eckrich and Sons) (Box B&B 16)
    - E. F. Hutton and Co., 1982-1984 (Box B&B 16)
    - Emery Worldwide (Emery Air Freight Corp.), 1982, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Fiat Motors of North America, 1981, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Florida Citrus commission, 1962 (Box B&B 16)
    - General Foods Corp.
      - Dessert Division: Birds Eye Cool Whip Non-Dairy Whipped Topping, 1980-1982 (Box B&B 16)
      - Maxwell House Division
        - Brim Decaffeinated Coffee, 1980-1982; Here's to Veterans, awards to client and B&B from U.S. Veterans Administration, 1950s? (Box B&B 16)
        - Maxwell House Radio Showboat, 1933, May (Box B&B 16)
      - Memorandum: to Ralph Starr Butler, General Foods, from Chester Bowles of B&B regarding the use of coupons, 1931, Sept. 10 (Box B&B 16)
      - Report: Production of Television and Radio Commercials prepared for (Box B&B 16)
    - General Petroleum Co. of California, Mobil Oil, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber co. (see Oversize Series) (Box B&B 16)
    - Hardee's Food Systems, 1980-1985 (Box B&B 16)
    - H.C. Moores Co., Division of M&R Dietetic Laboratories/Pream Instant Coffee Cream, 1962 (Box B&B 16)
    - Jos. Garneau Co./Bolla Wines, 1984 (Box B&B 16)
    - Jos. Schlitz Brewing Co./Schiltz Malt Liquor, 1980, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Lenox, 1950, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Mobil Oil (see General Petroleum of California) (Box B&B 16)
    - Muscular Dystrophy Association, 1981, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Mutual Life Insurance Co., undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Nabisco (see Standard Brands) (Box B&B 16)
    - Norwich-Eaton Pharmaceutical Co./Pepto Bismol, 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box B&B 16)
    - Peter Eckrich and Sons, 1981, undated (Box B&B 16)
    - Planters Products (see Standard Brands) (Box B&B 16)
    - Procter & Gamble Co. (Box B&B 17)
      - Charmin Bathroom Tissue: 15th Year Celebration
        - 1979-1981 (Box B&B 17)
        - Pictures, 1979-1981 (Box B&B 17)
      - Prell, 1962 (Box B&B 17)
      - Scope and Zest, 1980-1981 (Box B&B 17)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1941-1958 (Box B&B 17)
    - Prudential Insurance Co. of America
      - "Great Composers, Six Radio Dramatizations, presented on The Family Hour, 1943 (Box B&B 17)
    - Schlitz (see Jos. Schiltz) (Box B&B 17)
    - Standard Brands, Planters Products (Nabisco)
      - Planters Nuts
        - 1979-1982 (Box B&B 17)
        - Eva Gabor & Smothers, 1979-1982 (Box B&B 17)
      - Planters Oil, 1979 (Box B&B 17)
    - Stroh (see Jos. Schlitz) (Box B&B 17)
    - Texaco, 1962-1980 (Box B&B 17)
    - Western Electric Co., 1945 (Box B&B 17)
  - Meetings, 1967-1982 (bulk 1967-1977)
    Contains speeches and agendas. See also oversize materials. Arranged by type of meeting and then chronologically.
    - International Conferences (Box B&B 17)
      - 1967, Jan. 17, [First Annual Business Planning Conference], address by L. T. Steele (Box B&B 17)
      - 1968, Jan. 16-20, Second Annual Business Planning Conference, program and address by L. T. Steele (Box B&B 17)
      - 1970, Jan. 19-23, Fourth Annual Business Planning Conference, program and addresses by L. T. Steele and Victor G. Bloede (Box B&B 17)
    - International Conferences (Box B&B 18)
      - 1971, Jan. 19-22, Fifth Annual Business Planning Conference, address by L. T. Steele (Box B&B 18)
      - 1972, Jan. 22-28, sixth Annual Business Planning Conference, address by L. T. Steele (Box B&B 18)
      - 1973, Jan. 26 Seventh[?] Annual Business Planning Conference, address by L. T. Steele, The Future of B&B International (Box B&B 18)
      - 1977, May 10, Eleventh[?] Annual Business Planning Conference, address by Victor G. Bloede (Box B&B 18)
      - Stockholders Meetings, 1967-1982, 8 folders (Box B&B 18)
  - Clippings, 1980-1985
    Includes clipping compilations and loose clippings. Arranged by title of the compilation, then chronologically. Loose clippings arranged in chronological order. See also oversize materials.
    - Compilations: B&B in the News, 1980, Nov.-1982, Dec, 2 folders (Box B&B 18)
    - Compilations: B&B in the News, 1983, June-1984, April, 3 folders (Box B&B 19)
    - Compilations: B&B Publicity Reports, 1982-1985, 5 folders (Box B&B 19)
  - History, circa 1957-1979, undated (bulk 1967-1978)
    Contains company history research files and manuscripts that were created by three Benton & Bowles staff members: Atherton Hobler, Frank Smith, and Gordon Webber. Arranged into three categories: Atherton W. Hobler Autobiographies, Frank Smith Project, and Gordon Webber Project, Our Kind of People.
    - Atherton W. Hobler Autobiographies, 1960s-1970s
      Includes manuscripts and some correspondence. Includes information about Hobler's earlier advertising work with the Gardner Advertising Company. Hobler's writings include information about the development of Benton & Bowles advertising campaigns for clients, such as General Foods (Maxwell House Coffee, Cool Whip), the Florida Citrus Commission, Procter & Gamble (Ivory Snow, Pampers, Prell, Scope, Tide, Zest), S. C. Johnson & Son (Pledge), and Vick Chemical Co. (Nyquil), and information about company operations and the activities of its executives. Hobler's career is also documented in the Officers and Staff Series (Biographical Information). Arranged with draft manuscripts first, followed by correspondence and chapter drafts.
      - Education of One Advertising Man, circa 1967 (Box B&B 19)
      - I Saw the Change, draft outline for manuscript, 1960s? (Box B&B 19)
      - The Triangle of Marketing Success Manuscript, 1970s (Box B&B 19)
      - The Triangle of Marketing Success (Box B&B 20)
        - Drafts of chapters, 1971 (Box B&B 20)
        - Correspondence, circa 1967-1971 (Box B&B 20)
    - Frank Smith Project, 1967-1968, undated
      Includes manuscript drafts, notes, correspondence, memoranda, manuals, printed material, clippings, transcriptions, and press releases. There are a few original research notes; materials consist primarily of resource materials collected from B&B company files and manuscript drafts. Frank Smith's manuscript was not published. Arranged by form of draft (e.g., first draft), followed by correspondence, memoranda, and resource materials about various time periods. See also oversize material.
      - First draft, 1968 (Box B&B 20)
        - Background and Status Report; objectives of the history (Box B&B 20)
        - Title; cover design; preface; Chapter I, The Beginnings of the Business (Box B&B 20)
        - Chapter II, Bill Benton; Chapter III, Chet Bowles (Box B&B 20)
        - Chapter IV, 1930-1931 (Box B&B 20)
        - Chapter V, 1932; Chapter VI, Hobe [Hobler]; Chapter VII, 1933-1936 (Box B&B 20)
      - Manuscript draft and notes, 1968
        - Chapter I and II, Bill Benton (pp. 1-59), 2 folders (Box B&B 20)
      - Manuscript draft and notes, 1968 (Box B&B 21)
        - Chapter II, Bill Benton (pp. 1-15) (Box B&B 21)
        - Part II, Bill Benton (pp. 98-223) (Box B&B 21)
        - Chapter III, Chester Bowles, 2 folders (Box B&B 21)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1968-1969 (Box B&B 21)
      - Resource materials about 1930, 1941-1968, undated, 3 folders (Box B&B 21)
      - Resource materials 1948-1971, undated, 4 folders (Box B&B 22)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box B&B 22)
    - Gordon Webber Project, Our Kind of People, 1960s-1979
      Includes audio tapes, printed material, and advertisements. Contains research for Our Kind of People: The Story of the First 50 Years at Benton & Bowles, published by Benton & Bowles for its 50th anniversary in 1979The audiotapes of Webber's interviews with B&B executives provide personal views of the company's history. Also includes advertisements that were considered, but not used, for illustrations in the book. Arranged with published volume first, followed by the original manuscripts, and then research by type of material. See also oversize materials.
      - Our Kind of People: The Story of the First 50 Years at Benton & Bowles, 1979 (1 vol.) (Box B&B 22)
      - Our Kind of People: Original manuscript, 1978? (pp. 1-92) (Box B&B 22)
      - Our Kind of People (Box B&B 23)
        - Original manuscript, 1978? (pp. 93-276), 3 folders (Box B&B 23)
        - Index to audio tapes of interviews, 1978-1978 (Box B&B 23)
        - Interview tapes
          - Benton, Bill with Martha Deane, 1970, May 14 (Box B&B 23)
          - Bloede, Vic., 1978, Aug. 9-30 (3 tapes) (Box B&B 23)
          - Bowen, Jack, 1978, Sept. 26 (2 tapes (Box B&B 23)
          - Casey, Dick, 1978, Oct. 12 (Box B&B 23)
          - Ende, Dick, 1978, Sept. 21 (Box B&B 23)
          - Fescina, Andy, 1978, Dec. 15 (Box B&B 23)
          - Gilbert, A. M. (Gil), 1978, Aug. 15, Sept. 6 (4 tapes) (Box B&B 23)
          - Hamel, Al, 1978, Sept. 12 (2 tapes) (Box B&B 23)
      - Our Kind of People (Box B&B 24)
        - Interview tapes (continued)
          - Lind, Ray; McKenzie, R. L., 1978, Oct. 11, Nov. 12 (2 tapes (Box B&B 24)
          - McDermott, Tom, 1978, Oct. 3 (2 tapes) (Box B&B 24)
          - Pattison, Pat, 1978, Oct. 4 (2 tapes) (Box B&B 24)
          - Rich, Lee, 1978, Oct. 2 (Box B&B 24)
          - Rogers, Jim, 1978, Nov. 2 (Box B&B 24)
          - Schneeberg, Ed, 1978, Oct. 11 (2 tapes) (Box B&B 24)
          - Schneider, Bill, 1978, Oct. 11 (Box B&B 24)
          - Scofield, Helen, 1978, Sept. 7 (Box B&B 24)
          - Sidnam, Alan, 1978, Sept. 19 (2 tapes) (Box B&B 24)
          - Smith, Frank, 1978, Oct. 24 (2 tapes) (Box B&B 24)
          - Speer, David, 1978, Dec. 21 (Box B&B 24)
          - Steele, Ted, 1978, Aug. 17, July 27, Aug. 25 (5 tapes) (Box B&B 24)
          - Tompkins, Bill, 1978, Sept. 13, 17 (2 tapes) (Box B&B 24)
      - Jingle Jam, presentation by Pat Pattison, 1957, Mar1 (Box B&B 24)
      - Staff meeting, 1957, Feb. 26 (Box B&B 24)
      - Our Kind of People (Box B&B 25)
        - Library research, 1960s-1979 (Box B&B 25)
        - Resource material: Medicus Communications, B&B Production Dept., Personnel Dept., Promotion Dept., and Miscellaneous, 1978, undated (Box B&B 25)
        - Illustrations, not used in book, undated, 2 folders (Box B&B 25)
        - Illustrations, used in book, undated, 2 folders (Box B&B 25)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1929-circa 1980, undated
    Includes certificates, printed material, correspondence, invitations, photographs, a video cassette and reports. Arranged alphabetically by subject. See also oversize materials.
    - Awards, circa 1980 (Box B&B 26)
    - The Bowen Road Show: History of D-MM and B&B, undated (Box B&B 26)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box B&B 26)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary of Benton & Bowles
      - Dinner Invitation, circa 1979 (Box B&B 26)
      - Our Fiftieth Anniversary Year, A Photographic Record, 1979 (Box B&B 26)
    - Financial papers
      - Benton & Bowles Passbooks, 1929-1935 (Box B&B 26)
      - Fiscal Development Retrospective, 1930-1935 (Box B&B 26)
    - Harvard College, Harvard Business School: Case Studies of Benton & Bowles, 1966 (Box B&B 26)
    - World War II effort, 1943 (Box B&B 26)
    - Pictures
      - New York Office building, 909 Third [Ave.?], undated (Box B&B 26)
      - Corporate airplanes, 1948-1960s (Box B&B 26)
- D'Arcy-MacManus Masius, 1972-1985, undated
  Contains a chronological history of D'Arcy Advertising and its mergers that formed D'Arcy-MacManus Masius (D-MM); a profile directory that provides information relative to the D-MM Worldwide group of advertising agencies, biographical and historical notes, and clippings about the company.
  - Corporate Publications (Box D-MM 1)
    - Between Us, 75th Anniversary Edition, circa 1981 (Box D-MM 1)
    - Profiles
      - Information contacts, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - Introduction, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - DM&M worldwide, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - Africa, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - Australasia/Far East, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - Europe, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - Latin/South America, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - North America, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
      - Inter-Ad, 1982 (Box D-MM 1)
  - Notes/manuscript: Biographical information for William C. D'Arcy and Leonard Masius, undated (Box D-MM 1)
  - Notes/manuscript: History of company, undated (Box D-MM 1)
  - Clippings, 1972, Oct. 16-1985, July 1, undated (Box D-MM 1)
- D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, 1985-1989 and undated, 6 boxes
  - Memoranda, 1985-1986
    Includes directives and announcements that were issued by the New York and Corporate Offices about events, policies, procedures, personnel changes, benefits, employee recreation, and other company business. Arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - 1985, Sept.-1986, Oct, 2 folders (Box DMB&B 1)
  - Reports, 1980s-1986
    Contains two major research reports and related clippings.
    - Belief Dynamics... A Discipline for Managing Beliefs and Behavior, 1980s (Box DMB&B 1)
    - Fear and Fantasies of the American Consumer, An American Consensus Report, 1986, May (Box DMB&B 1)
    - Clipping index and summary, 1986, June 17 (Box DMB&B 1)
    - Clipping Vol. I and II (Supplements), 1986, 2 folders (Box DMB&B 1)
  - Officers and Staff, 1986-1988
    Contains staff resources printed material and related correspondence. Arranged chronologically. See also oversize materials.
    - 1986, Corporate Out-of-Home Medical Department Catalog (Box DMB&B 2)
    - 1987, Chairman's Report to Employee, sent to company employees (Box DMB&B 2)
    - 1988, Feb., Management Directory (Box DMB&B 2)
  - Corporate Publications, 1985-1988
    Adventures and Momentum are house organs and convey primarily internal news. Includes printed material and related correspondence. Arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically. See also oversize materials.
    - Annual Report, 1988 (Box DMB&B 2)
    - Adventures (formerly NY Adventures, 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box DMB&B 2)
    - Adventures artwork, 1986, April (Clients: Procter & Gamble, FTD-San Diego Chicken) (Box DMB&B 2)
    - DMB&B: A Celebrated New Force... (inaugural edition), 1985, Oct (Box DMB&B 2)
    - Momentum, 1986-1988, 1 folders (Box DMB&B 2)
  - Clients, undated
    Contains story boards, photographs, and negatives.
    - MCI Communications Corp., undated (Box DMB&B 2)
  - Meetings, 1987
    Contains speeches given at the DMB&B Worldwide Management Meeting in 1987Arranged alphabetically by name of speaker.
    - DMB&B Worldwide Management Meeting, 1987, Apr. 30 (Box DMB&B 2)
      - Bostock, Roy, The U.S. Division (Box DMB&B 2)
      - Redwell, Peter, The International Division (Box DMB&B 2)
      - Simko, George, The Diversified Communications Companies (Box DMB&B 2)
  - Clippings, 1985-1989
    News and events related to DMB&B and its clients through articles that were compiled on a monthly schedule and distributed as press clipping books to the Worldwide Management executives. Also contains some loose clippings. Arranged chronologically.
    - Merger, 1985 (Box DMB&B 2)
    - Compilations: 1985-1986, Feb. 3, 3 folders (Box DMB&B 2)
    - Compilation: 1986, Apr.-July, 4 folders (Box DMB&B 3)
    - Compilation: 1986, Aug.-Nov. 9, undated, 6 folders (Box DMB&B 4)
    - Compilation: 1986, Nov. 10-1987, Jan, 6 folders (Box DMB&B 5)
    - DMB&B in the News, (clipping book), 1989, May (Box DMB&B 5)
  - Pictures, 1985-1986
    Includes photographic prints, contact prints, negatives, transparencies, and a memorandum. Primarily documents the company's officers and staff, including those at subsidiary companies. Photographs of staff at merger celebrations worldwide form about one-half of the materials. The theme We're So Excited is displayed on banners held by staff in many of the merger photographs. Includes pictures of the DMB&B Worldwide Management meeting and other meetings. Also includes photographs of the staff of Benton & Bowles subsidiary companies. Arranged in four sections: Officers and Staff, in chronological order; Merger-related events, by office location, U.S. and internationally; and Miscellaneous subjects, in chronological order.
    - Officers and Staff (Box DMB&B 5)
      - 1985-1986, Portraits: Michael Dabrowski, Erica Gillespie, Joel Harrison, Tom Lentz, Joel Maliniak, Steve Marlow, Red Norman, Andrew Salzman, Dave Williamson (Box DMB&B 5)
      - 1986, Jan. 29, Mary Snyder's retirement party (New York Office) (Box DMB&B 5)
      - 1986, Mar. 11, John S. Bowen's presentation and reception (New York Office) (Box DMB&B 5)
      - 1986, Employee Relations Committee (Box DMB&B 5)
      - 1986, United Way 1985fund drive winners (Box DMB&B 5)
    - Meetings (Box DMB&B 6)
      - 1986, Jan. 20, Board of Directors (Box DMB&B 6)
      - 1986, Apr7, Board presentation (Box DMB&B 6)